thingsremembered.com 2014-04-20

# Privacy and Security at Things Remembered

At Things Remembered your trust and satisfaction is of the utmost importance. We are committed to respecting the privacy and the security of your personal information and have instituted policies intended to ensure that your personal information is handled in a safe and responsible manner. This Policy was last revised on October 7, 2013.

* * *

## Mailing Lists

From time to time, we make our mailing list (including names and addresses only) and general shopping activities available to carefully selected companies whose products or services we believe may be of interest to you and whose privacy practices meet the Direct Marketing Association's privacy standards. We do not share email addresses for this purpose. If you do not wish to receive mailings from these carefully selected companies, simply call Customer Service at 866.902.4438.

**Back to top**

## Personal Information

We may also share your personal information, and any transactions you conduct on our site or offline with us with a third-party advertising partner and its service providers in order to deliver you advertising tailored to your interests when you visit certain other websites. Data shared with our third-party partner is made anonymous. If you wish to not have your information shared for these purposes, please contact us at 866.902.4438.

**Back to top**

## Security of Your Information

Rest assured that we utilize the latest encryption technology to ensure the safety of your personal information at Things Remembered. Your ordering information (name, address, credit card, etc.) is encrypted during the ordering process & transmission, using our secure server to provide the highest level of security possible. In addition, once received, your credit card data is stored on a server that cannot be accessed via the Internet.

We further protect your information using the following methods:

  * **Password protection:** When you create an account with us, your password creates another level of security for your personal information. Your password is your secret code into your account. Make your password a combination of at least 6 (no more than 10) characters/numbers that are not easily guessed (don't make your password your last name, for example). 
  * **Site protection:** Our entire site is protected behind an advanced firewall (think of it as a cyber fortress), which prevents unauthorized persons from accessing your information.

**Back to top**

## Updating Your Information

Creating a thingsremembered.com account allows you to take advantage of the unique services that thingsremembered.com offers, including email newsletters with exclusive offers, the ability to view your order history and track your orders, and the ability to keep a convenient address book for faster checkout. We pledge to keep your confidential information confidential. To protect your privacy, we will need to validate your identity before you update or review your information. 

**Back to top**

## How We Use Your Email Address

We are proud to be 100% compliant with the 2004 Can SPAM act, meaning that we do not send unsolicited email to our customers. It is our intent to send promotional emails only to those persons who wish to receive them. We do not sell or rent your email information to outside parties. At Things Remembered, your email address is used in the following ways: 

  * Order and Shipment Confirmation Emails: When you place an order, we will send you an email that indicates that we have received your order (order confirmation) and a later email that indicates that your order has been shipped (shipment confirmation). 
  * Email Newsletters and Promotions: When you provide your email address to us at thingsremembered.com, you will be asked if you want to receive special offers from us via email. If you indicate that you do not want to receive email offers from us, rest assured that you will not receive information from us.

**Back to top**

## Email Unsubscribe

If you have provided your email address to us and have elected to receive special offers and promotions via email, but would like to discontinue receiving these special offers and promotions, simply click on the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom of a Things Remembered email and follow the unsubscribe instructions. You may also call 866.902.4438 for assistance.

Please note that when you make a purchase and provide us with your email address, we may send you confirmation of your order via email even if you have chosen not to receive email from us about special offers and promotions. We may also contact you by mail or telephone if we have questions about your order.

**Back to top**

## Cookies

Thingsremembered.com uses your browser's "cookie" feature. A cookie is a small piece of text stored on a computer by a web browser. As text, cookies are not executable and therefore cannot replicate themselves and are not viruses. Cookies are used to ensure that items remain in your Shopping Bag while you continue shopping and to keep track of site preferences like your display name, home store and other session information. We do not use cookies to store personal information such as your credit card number.. We may use technologies such as our own cookies to provide you with enhanced online display advertising tailored to your interests. To opt out of advertising provided by us, click [here](http://dtmc.thingsremembered.com/adinfo/adchoices_fpc.html?cid=2547&cname=Things%20Remembered&cmagic=86ecfc&clogo=things_remembered.png). 

Cookies enable you to take advantage of some of our most valuable services. In accordance with our Privacy Policy, the information contained in your thingsremembered.com cookie is confidential, never shared, and is used to enhance your shopping experience while on our website. Please note that certain pages of the Site may not function properly if cookies are turned off. Please consult your web browser's Help documentation for more information about how to turn cookies on and off within your browser.

We may use third party companies to assist us in understanding shoppers use of the site and to provide online display advertising tailored to their interests. To accomplish this, these companies may place cookies on your computer to receive information about your browsing and buying activity on the site, and help us to provide you with a better, more personalized shopping experience. We prohibit these companies from using this information for their own marketing purposes or from sharing this information with anyone other than Things Remembered. To learn more, or to opt-out of receiving advertisements tailored to your interests, visit the Network Advertising Initiative at www.networkadvertising.org/choices. 

**Back to top**
